<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data on Experiment In Art</title>
    <link>/tags/data/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data on Experiment In Art</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3 first steps for better integrated analytics</title>
      <link>/post/3-first-steps-for-better-integrated-analytics./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/3-first-steps-for-better-integrated-analytics./</guid>
      <description>The negative effects of having loosely connected analytics teams who do not work closely together are felt in two areas:
 Consumers of analytics waste time in understanding and therefore acting on information, arguably making worse decisions.
 Creators of analytics waste time in re-work, re-explaining and general circular grinding of gears having work understood by decision makers.  Despite this, it is not uncommon to find multiple analytics teams working in parallel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How thinking like a games developer can take data transformation to the next level</title>
      <link>/post/how-thinking-like-a-games-developer-can-take-data-transformation-to-the-next-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-thinking-like-a-games-developer-can-take-data-transformation-to-the-next-level/</guid>
      <description>This article first appeared in Consultancy Asia
Modern organisations must move from being reactive to proactive with the handling of their data assets, and use those assets in service of their customers. Easy to say and yet harder to do, and we all benefit from casting a wide net to inspire our own learning through doing.
In Asia, we have the most gaming-savvy population in the world. We were raised on Nintendo, we watch e-sports and play online more than anywhere else on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Things Data Science Teams Can Learn From Creative Teams</title>
      <link>/post/5-things-data-science-teams-can-learn-from-creative-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/5-things-data-science-teams-can-learn-from-creative-teams/</guid>
      <description>Many data science teams struggle to solve problems that have not been well defined. They are often left to their own devices to sift through information until they strike gold, or else are subject to an ever-evolving string of ‘requirements’ which generally focus on what and how, ignoring why and for who. Additionally, they may struggle to set up, structure and ultimately sell their solution to an audience of mixed experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>