<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experiment In Art</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Experiment In Art</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2020 goals</title>
      <link>/post/january-2020-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/january-2020-goals/</guid>
      <description>Write and submit one short story
Skip 12,000 times
Complete Jocko&amp;rsquo;s Beginner Series One Workout in under 60mins
Solve all 101 problems in &amp;lsquo;Basic Probability&amp;rsquo; section of &amp;lsquo;Schaum&amp;rsquo;s Outlines: Probability and Statistics&amp;rsquo;
Complete up to lesson 233 in Typing Club &amp;lsquo;Typing Jungle&amp;rsquo; course</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading list</title>
      <link>/post/reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/reading-list/</guid>
      <description> I want to be a more considered and intentional reader, so I am going to record each book that I read. That is what a considered and intentional reader would do, right? I do not include study textbooks in this list.
Summary    Category Title Author Date_start Date_end Skulls Notes     Non Fiction The Tao Is Silent Raymond M. Smullyan 2019-11-01 TBC 0 TBC   Non Fiction The Joy Of Less Francine Jay 2019-12-31 TBC 0 TBC   Fiction Annihilation Jeff VanDermeer 2019-12-31 TBC 0 TBC    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My daily writing habit</title>
      <link>/post/my-daily-writing-habit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/my-daily-writing-habit/</guid>
      <description>“Words are to writers as clay is to sculptors.”
― (Old Jungle Saying)
 Each morning I wrestle with my computer for exactly ten minutes and crank out some sentences. I have learned that I can deliver around 500 words in this timeframe. This is seemingly the maximum output my brain and two-finger clawhammer typing technique can muster. For now.
I have been writing for many years in a sporadic fashion including publishing a few short stories and more than a few songs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Warpath</title>
      <link>/warpath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/warpath/</guid>
      <description>I am at war with the demons that lurk inside of me.
They are crafty and patient and relentless. They change their tactics and exploit any weakness to achieve their objectives.
Sometimes I give them names to make it easier to disassociate and gather my strength against them. Sometimes I lament their existence and turn their qualities into aspects of my art. Pain, frustration, regret, fear; these can all be used to counterpoint and accentuate joy, forgiveness and peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things</title>
      <link>/things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/things/</guid>
      <description>This is my body of work.
Willie McRae Danger Dreams. A collection of short stories.
Tales From The Edge Of Reality. Zombies, intergalactic truck drivers, seduction, betrayal&amp;hellip;.
The Way It Goes. Acoustic song with some ghosts singing in the background.
Gumeracha Frog. Experimental country music about frogs, zombies and having a good time.
Orlac Wizard Extreme Power And Wealth. Part one of a seven part musical epic about a wizard from the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Experiment: to try something in order to discover what it is like or find out more about it.
Art: an activity through which people express particular ideas.
This is my blog about living life and making things.
You can find me on Twitter.
CREDITS:
Thanks to blogdown: Creating Websites with R Markdown for explaining how to set this website up.
Thanks to Luiz F. A. de Prá for the Coder theme and Yusiki Ishimi for extending it into the Coder-Portfolio theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>