<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experiment In Art</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Experiment In Art</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3 first steps for better integrated analytics</title>
      <link>/post/3-first-steps-for-better-integrated-analytics./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/3-first-steps-for-better-integrated-analytics./</guid>
      <description>The negative effects of having loosely connected analytics teams who do not work closely together are felt in two areas:
 Consumers of analytics waste time in understanding and therefore acting on information, arguably making worse decisions.
 Creators of analytics waste time in re-work, re-explaining and general circular grinding of gears having work understood by decision makers.  Despite this, it is not uncommon to find multiple analytics teams working in parallel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How thinking like a games developer can take data transformation to the next level</title>
      <link>/post/how-thinking-like-a-games-developer-can-take-data-transformation-to-the-next-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-thinking-like-a-games-developer-can-take-data-transformation-to-the-next-level/</guid>
      <description>This article first appeared in Consultancy Asia
Modern organisations must move from being reactive to proactive with the handling of their data assets, and use those assets in service of their customers. Easy to say and yet harder to do, and we all benefit from casting a wide net to inspire our own learning through doing.
In Asia, we have the most gaming-savvy population in the world. We were raised on Nintendo, we watch e-sports and play online more than anywhere else on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Things Data Science Teams Can Learn From Creative Teams</title>
      <link>/post/5-things-data-science-teams-can-learn-from-creative-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/5-things-data-science-teams-can-learn-from-creative-teams/</guid>
      <description>Many data science teams struggle to solve problems that have not been well defined. They are often left to their own devices to sift through information until they strike gold, or else are subject to an ever-evolving string of ‘requirements’ which generally focus on what and how, ignoring why and for who. Additionally, they may struggle to set up, structure and ultimately sell their solution to an audience of mixed experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Deliver My Daily Words</title>
      <link>/post/how-i-deliver-my-daily-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-i-deliver-my-daily-words/</guid>
      <description>“Words are to writers as clay is to sculptors.”
― (Old Jungle Saying)
 Each morning I wrestle with my computer for exactly ten minutes and crank out some sentences. I have learned that I can deliver around 500 words in this timeframe. This is seemingly the maximum output my brain and two-finger clawhammer typing technique can muster. For now.
I have been writing for many years in a sporadic fashion including publishing a few short stories and more than a few songs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Warpath</title>
      <link>/warpath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/warpath/</guid>
      <description>I am at war with the demons that lurk inside of me.
They are crafty and patient and relentless. They change their tactics and exploit any weakness to achieve their objectives.
Sometimes I give them names to make it easier to disassociate and gather my strength against them. Sometimes I lament their existence and turn their qualities into aspects of my art. Pain, frustration, regret, fear; these can all be used to counterpoint and accentuate joy, forgiveness and peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things</title>
      <link>/things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/things/</guid>
      <description>Over the years I have built a small body of work.
It is my quest in life to defeat my demons of distraction and negativity and become more prolific and generous.
Words Willie McRae Danger Dreams
Morning Vultures
Cold Black Magic
From Alcatraz To Charon
The Grim Tale Of Mr Lightfoot
The Omega Automatic Seamasters Cosmic
Nereyda
Red Highway
The Stick And The Trick
The Walk
Pomodori Galactic
Marmalade And Rhymes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Experiment: to try something in order to discover what it is like or find out more about it.
Art: an activity through which people express particular ideas.
Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Will Bidstrup, welcome to my blog about living life and making things.
You can also find me on Twitter.
CREDITS:
Thanks to blogdown: Creating Websites with R Markdown for explaining how to set this website up.
Thanks to Luiz F. A. de Prá for the Coder theme and Yusiki Ishimi for extending it into the Coder-Portfolio theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>